



Sydney, NSW (0)





linkedin.com/in/kennethcdlc/ in





SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a software engineer with 2 years of experience in electrical system design and implementation. Finding my love for tech, I am transitioning these skills in software engineering to create and build admirable software applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

General Assembly | 2022

Software Engineer

Intensive 12 week (480+ hour) course covering fundamentals in full-stack software development.

Project 3: Pokemon Quizzr | Github | Live Site

Pokemon Quizzr is a web guiz app that lets you browse and search all 898 pokemon on the Pokedex, play a quiz game from any pokemon generation of your choice, and tracks your score to be display on the Leaderboard. Tech Stack: React JS, Firebase, Firestore, Pokemon API

Project 2: Expense Trackr | Github | Live Site

In this group project, the team collaborated to make an Expense Trackr application that helps you to organize your finances keeping track of all your expenses and incomes. React JS was utilised to build the frontend and Ruby on Rails for the backend.

Project 1: Manga-shoppu | Github | Live Site

Manga-shoppu is an e-commerce web application project that I made using Ruby on Rails that allows users to purchase different kind of mangas. Admin users can add and edit product description, image, prices, and stock quantities. While users can add products to their carts, have a subtotal and total costs on their cart and checkout.

Project 0: Tic Tac Toe | Github | Live Site

Utilised Javascript, CSS, HTML and jQUery to make a fun TicTacToe game project that lets you play 1v1 and demonstrates a nice responsive UI.

Canva | 2019-2022

Junior Chef

Utilised Stakeholder management and communication skills to ensure a positive customer experience.

Dream Makers Construction | 2015-2017 Field Electrical Engineer

- Managed costs and resources to meet construction budget.
- Designed revisions and additional works using AutoCAD.
- Identified labour and material cost revisions on electrical works.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Express.js HTML / CSS •
 - Node.js JavaScript •
- MongoDB Ruby •
- Ruby on Rails React.is •
 - Firebase Vue.js •
 - Firestore Bootstrap •
 - Sinatra Semantic UI •
 - SOL Framer Motion •
 - PostgreSQL iQuery •
 - RESTful API Netlify •
 - Heroku •
 - Cloudinary •
 - Git/Github •

EDUCATION

2022

Software Engineering Immersive

General Assembly

2018-2019

Master of Project Management

Central Queensland University

2010 - 2015 **Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering Bulacan State University**